影视强哥 制作压制
这么多人
So many people!
你的臭点子行不行？
You think your idea will work?
拼拼看
Let's try!
为了你，拼就拼吧
l'll do it because of you.
让开…
Step aside...
让开！对不起！
Step aside, give way!
让一让
Give way please...
你们两个干什么？干什么？
What are you two doing?
快去找救兵…
Hurry up, go get some help.
你们干什么…
What are you doing?
你别紧张
Take it easy, will you?
你不要拉，会摔死你
Don't pull! l'll make you fall!
停车！你带我去哪？
Stop! Where are you taking me?
走开，快放了我！哥，救我！
Go away, let me go! George, help me!
哥哥，小心点…
George, be careful. Be careful, please.
对不起，我从电影学回来的
Sorry, l learned it from the movies.
干什么…
What are you trying to do?
拜拜
Bye!
搞定
Finished!
你们快点停！放开我…
Stop it, you guys, let me go...
糟了！停车了！
Damn it! Stop!
干什么？
What's the matter?
没有油了
We're out of gas!
你也够笨了，现在告诉我没有油
ldiot! We're out of gas now?
我怎么知道要走这么远呢
How was l to know we were going so far?
身上又没有带什么钱 就随便的加一点
l don't have any cash on me. Just add a little.
金刚呀，她老是噜了噜了的 说什么呀？
king kong, she's been saying ''Lok'' all day long. What does ''Lok'' mean in Thai?
我怎么知道她说什么？
-How would l know? -She is doing it again.
糟了…！没油了！
Damn, we're out of gas!
快把油门加到底
To low gear, quick!
没有油怎么加？
We've run out. l can't get it started.
金刚，好多人，怎么办？
They're coming, king kong! What shall we do?
我打死你！我打！
l'm going to kill you!
我挡不住了！
l can't take anymore!
接好，绑紧点
Hold it! Tie her up.
金刚，你说你对女人最行了
You said you were best at handling women!
你搞定她吧
You handle her!
我那来功夫搞她，先把马搞定吧
l'm busy, let's fix the horse first.
要我去那里？混蛋，放开我！
Where are you taking me? Let me go!
动了…！
Move, move.
快救我…
Help me, help me!
好厉害呀！好爽啊！
How wonderful!
比罗宾汉更厉害
lt's more exciting than ''Ben Hur''.
对啊…
Right, right!
救我！
Help me!
你别搅和了
Stop it!
停车，放了我，快把我放了！
Stop the car! Let me go!
放了我…混蛋，停车！
Bastard, stop the car! Let me go!
停车，放我！
Let me go!
快出来，快点…
Hurry up!
带我去那？干什么？
Where are you taking me?
金刚，你抱住她 别让她再烦了
king kong, hold her tight! Don't let her push me again,
不然我要掉到水里去了
Or else we'll drop into the water.
知道了
Alright!
你别吵了，是你老公Mr.Zoombut
Quiet! Your husband, Mr. Zoombut,
给我们钱，叫我们救你的
paid us to save you.
你老公给钱，叫我们救你的
Your husband paid us to save you!
不，Mr.Zoombut不是我老公
Mr. Zoombut is not my husband.
他给我妈妈一大笔钱买我的
He paid my mother a lot of money to get me.
所以我兴男朋友私奔结婚
So l ran off to marry my boyfriend.
行了行了，搞定了
Everything's fine.
快来，下来下来，小姐，发财了！
Come on, girl, go...
光头佬，我们弄错了
Baldy, we've made a mistake.
他妈妈强逼她嫁给凯子
Her mother forced her to marry an old man.
她跟她男朋友私奔出来结婚的
She eloped with her boyfriend.
你说什么？
What did you say?
这种不义之财 我们最佳拍档怎可赚呢
How can The Aces earn such money?
赚了以后，我们一辈子心也不安
We'd feel bad the rest of our lives!
你说什么屁话
Are you bullshitting?
还是把她送回去吧
Let's send her home first!
你有毛病！把她送回去？
Are you crazy? Send her home?
我死也要赚这笔钱
l want the money!
我把男人婆跟小光头送去移民
My wife and bald kid have emigrated,
我不收这笔钱 他们那里有钱买房子？
lf l don't get the money, how can l buy a house?
你不要拦着我
Don't stop me!
你活生生的把人家拆散 一点良心都没有
You're breaking them up? Where's your conscience?
还做什么英雄？
How can you be a hero?
我不做什么英雄
l don't want to be a hero!
了不起我帮新郎把他救回来
Let's rescue her back someday for the groom.
你要钱要疯了
You're money mad!
他来了
He's coming!
对不起，小姐，跟我来吧
Excuse me, lady, follow me!
光头佬，你不要这样嘛
Baldy, don't!
我尽量想办法帮你凑钱好了
l'll think of something for your mortgage!
你冷静一点
Calm down!
不要挡着！我发不了财就找你
Come on, come...
放手！别挡着我
Let me go! Don't block my way.
你听我说
Listen to me.
别动
Don't move!
死丫头
Bitch!
我买你回来，你竟敢跟人私奔？
l paid for you! But you dared to elope!
害得我丢死人了！你知道吗？
Do you know you made me lose face?
我肯娶你，是你的福份
You're lucky l want to marry you!
你真该死
Damn you!
大哥，大哥
George, George!
死丫头，你还想跟他走？
Bitch, you still want to go with him?
小妹
May!
走，去教训他，快点
Teach him a lesson! Quick!
小妹
May!
大哥…不要打他！
George, don't beat him!
别打我大哥！大哥…
Don't beat George! George!
杀了他…
kill him! kill him!
不！
No!
别动
Don't move!
小妹  别动他
-May! -Don't touch him!
别动
Don't move
走，走…
Go! Go! Hurry up.
快走吧
Move!
走吧，走…快走呀！
Go, go, hurry up, get out.
我付钱给你们
l paid you money,
但你居然敢出卖我
but you dared betray me?
最佳拍档，我会记住你们！
Aces, l'll remember you!
谢谢你们
Thank you!
快走吧，别[卡]了
Go, go...
拿你的钱去死吧！
Take your money and go to hell.
你有毛病，怎么会把钱还给他呢
Silly! How can you return the money to him?
干什么？吵什么？够了吧
Stop! lt's enough!
别动手动脚
Stop it, don't!
你打我？
You hit me!
光头佬，别乱来
Stop it, Baldy!
你别跟着我
Don't follow me.
我不认识你
l don't know you.
中国国宝秦始皇连兵马俑 及秦皇宝剑
The Terracotta Warriors and the Bronze Sword
以船运抵香港作第一次的展览
were shipped to Hk for public exhibition for the first time.
但在运抵货柜码头搬运途中
While they were being unloaded,
被贼人偷龙转凤，将国宝劫走
the White Gloves snatched them away.
阿弟，小心点
Ben, be careful!
你说什么？
What did you say?
我叫你小心点
l said, be careful!
你说了八百遍了
You've said that a thousand times!
你小心点呀
Just be careful!
知道了姐姐
Yes, my dear sis.
不要急，大家动作要快
Don't rush, but we have to move quickly!
快…快一点
Be quick!
搞定了，一切非常顺利
Ok, everything is going smoothly!
让我检查一下
Let's check it out.
是
Yes sir!
快点…
Hurry up, come on!
让我看看我的秦皇宝剑
Let me see my Chinese Excalibur!
是
Yes sir!
秦皇宝剑属于我的
The Excalibur...
秦皇宝剑，秦皇宝剑…
lt's all mine...
盒子
The box!
小心
Be careful!
是
Yes!
抓着他…
Get him! Get him!
分头追
Let's split!
是
Yes!
快点照相
Let's take some photos, quick!
阿弟，我们成功了
Ben! We made it!
走
Let's go!
进去
Get in!
快点
Hurry up!
行了
Ok!
快点
Hurry up!
最佳拍档？
Aces?
再见
Goodbye!
我们是新最佳拍档
We're the new Aces.
永远是新最佳拍档…
Forever, the new Aces.
署长，早
Uncle Wah, good morning!
什么事？
What's the matter?
兵马俑被人偷了
Uncle Wah, the Terracotta Army has been stolen.
我知道，可是你们这么急找我回来
l know. You paged me to come back.
跟什么人开会？
Who are we meeting with?
是跟大陆公安局的人开会
The representative of the Security Unit from China.
表叔？
Uncle?
他不是表叔，他是表弟
No, he's not uncle. He's our cousin!
他是公安局局长的儿子
He's the unit head's son.
而且他还是从美国留学回来的
He studied in the US for over 10 years.
大陆人叫他[中国蓝波]
ln China, they call him Chinese Rambo!
蓝波？
Rambo?
这么看来，这个会不好受
So it won't be an easy meeting!
请坐
Please have a seat.
这个是兵马俑的模型
This is a sample of the Terracotta Army.
一批真的在香港被抢了
The real ones have been stolen in Hk.
是两名自称[最佳拍档]的人做的
lt's done by the two men called The Aces.
还把照片寄到各大报馆
They even sent photos to the press,
要求刊登头条
and asked them to be put on the front page.
署长，你有什么看法？
Uncle Wah, what do you think?
这怎么可能？
lt's impossible!
你跟他们很熟？
You know them well! Right?
是，不过我很久没见过他们
Yes, but we haven't met for years.
不知道…
l don't know...
我知道
l know!
他们三年前拆了伙
They separated three years ago.
金刚改了行，开了家投资顾问公司
king kong started an investment company.
三年没有开过张
However, he has neither earned money
三年没有练过功夫
nor maintained his physical condition.
两年没有交过房租
He hasn't paid his rent for 2 years
一年没有发过薪水给秘书
and hasn't paid his secretary for a year.
对不对？
Am l right?
光头佬把老婆儿子送去加拿大移民
After sending his wife and son to Canada,
自己留在香港赚钱
Baldy stayed in Hk alone to earn money,
跑去炒股票，炒垮了
He got burnt at the stock market
欠了一屁股债，现在躲了起来
and he is now hiding from debtors
就躲在西贡德记渔场
in Sai kung.
我们的档案里没有这个纪录
None of that is on file!
不是没有，是你撕掉了几页
Yes, you shredded the pages.
请问，我们有什么可以帮你的？
What can we do for you?
有，只要你们不碍手碍脚
Yes, one thing. Just don't interrupt.
不去通风报讯
Don't let the secret out.
他们一定逃不出我的手心
They won't be able to get away from me!
这就好办了
lt's easy.
我们最喜欢睁一眼，闭一眼
We hate responsibility!
但金刚很狡猾
But king kong is very cunning,
你们怎么对付他？
are you prepared?
武力
Power!
最佳拍档，你们这一次倒霉了！
Aces, you are out of luck this time.
金刚
king kong!
艾伦，说了三年 叫你不要再叫我金刚
For the past 3 years, l've been telling you not to call me that.
我现在叫周围发嘛
Now l am called Ever Rich!
是，发哥，吃早点了
Yes, Brother Rich! Your breakfast.
我弄了一个早上，是法国名菜
lt took an hour to cook, it's a French dish.
又是些中看不中吃的东西
Those look beautiful but not edible.
那些花不能吃的
The flowers are not edible.
我知道，我闻一闻嘛
l know, l'll just smell it.
你用叉子嘛，干净卫生又浪漫
Use the fork please, it is more hygienic,
好有情调…
and more romantic...
等你呀，我都吃光了
l've finished eating and you're still talking.
有人来了
There's a client coming.
我去开门
Let me open the door.
等一等，我先把衣服穿上
Wait a second. Let me get dressed.
告诉你，我穿衣服的时候 不要故意偷看我
Don't peep.
你这样说，是叫我看还是不看？
You really don't want me to peep?
小妹妹
Hey little girl!
请你弄清楚我们的宾主关系
Let's be clear, we are colleagues.
我是上司，你是秘书
l am the boss, you are the secretary.
千万别把私人感情扯进去，知道吗？
Don't link it with personal affection.
这一年多你都没有给我薪水
You've not paid me for over a year,
每天还要弄早点给你吃
but l keep cooking breakfast for you everyday.
如果只是为了宾主关系
lf we're only employer and employee,
那你另请秘书好了
you better hire someone else!
知道吗？
Do you understand?
我知道
l do.
薪水先欠着嘛，等我赚到了钱
l'll pay you.
我就全部的、所有的 双倍的、Double的、全都还给你
When l make some money. You'd have to double it.
行了行了…快点…快点…
Ok... Hurry up.
开门了
l'll get the door.
股票财神爷，人家都这么叫我
People call me the God of Stocks.
认识我的人，全都发了
Friends who trust me become millionaires.
我的情报你都不信，你自找的
Find your own tips if you don't believe mine.
又损失了几千万吗？有客户来了！
You've lost 5 billion, right? Here comes my client.
嗨，你好，欢迎！
Hello, welcome.
刚才我有一个朋友不相信我的情报
A friend who didn't trust my tips just
所以损失了一千多万！
lost 5 billion.
昨晚上的事是你干的吗？
Are you the one who did ''The Thing'' last night?
我昨天晚上干了很多事
l did a lot of things last night.
你说那一件呢？
Which one do you mean?
兵马俑
The Terracotta Army!
兵马俑，你真有眼光
Terracotta Army! You're smart.
我早就想干了，现在流行
l've been thinking about it, lt's trendy.
你准备怎么做？
What do you want me to do?
兵马俑在那里？
Where is the Terracotta Army?
当然是在西安，难道在非洲？
ln Xian of course, where else?
我们这一家是投资公司
We're in the investment business.
我们先简简单单签份合约
Let's sign a contract first.
艾伦，来一份合约
Ellen, get a contract please.
先生，怎么称呼？
Sir, may l have your name?
中国蓝波
Chinese Rambo!
中国蓝波？
Chinese Rambo?
小姐，请你站远一点
Excuse me, please!
你抽根雪茄
Have a cigar first.
国宝你也敢偷
How dare you steal national treasures?
大家都是文明人，不要动手动脚
We are civilized people. Let's be calm.
等等，我要听电话
Wait, answer the phone first.
喂，署长
Hello, Sir!
华叔
Hello, Uncle Wah!
哈，华叔
好厉害呀，他就在我面前
Terrific! He's right before me.
什么？我自己搞定？祝我好运？
Settle this by myself? And good luck to me?
他说什么？
What did Uncle Wah say?
他说祝我好运
Good luck to me!
你不要逼我动手
Don't make me fight back!
金刚…
king kong...
你把兵马俑藏在那里？
Where did you hide the Terracotta Army?
艾伦，帮我把档案拿给他
Please check the file for me, Ellen.
在那里？
Where?
兵马俑在那？
Where is it?
你先放手，不然我怎样拿给你？
First, let go. How can l get it otherwise?
兵马俑藏在那里？快说！
Where is the Terracotta Army?
这边这边…快！
This way!
你不要逼人太甚，蓝球！
Quit shoving me, Basketball!
你说什么？
What did you call me?
我说你不是中国蓝波
l said you're not Chinese Rambo.
你是中国蓝球！
But Chinese Dumbo.
什么？
What?
真准，蓝波终于玩完了
Wonderful! Chinese Rambo is dead.
你还笑得那么开心
Why are you so happy?
你知不知道破坏了我的形象
Don't you know it destroyed my image?
我从来没玩出过人命的
l've never killed a man in my life.
快点找人来修理玻璃
Go get someone to fix the window.
快说
Tell me,
兵马俑在那里
where did you hide the Terracotta Army?
不要怕，他是不打女人的
Don't be afraid. He won't hit a woman.
继续努力，我一定会加你薪水的
keep on, l'll increase your salary!
对不起，我搭隔壁那一部，再见
l'm sorry. l'll take the other lift, bye!
好，我走楼梯就是了
No problem, l'll walk down from there.
你大哥在上面
Your big brother is up there!
够了，我翻脸了
l've enough! Do you want me to use force?
你们两个黑妞，别逼我揍你们
You two scoundrels, don't force me to fight you.
他说什么？
What did he say?
不知道
l don't know!
我说不要逼我动手打你们
l say don't force me to hit you!
他说要打
He says he will hit us.
打
Hit!
要人命呀？
Do you want to kill me?
太过份了…
Too much! lt's too much!
你好，金刚
Hi, king kong!
你不要吓我啊
Don't shock me!
说好了不叫我金刚的嘛
l've asked you not to call me king kong!
怎么了，又有人讨债啊？
What is it? Are your creditors after you again?
什么讨债？我在晨跑
What do mean? l'm justjogging.
再见
Bye!
妈的，你会不会开车！要人命啊？
Damn it, woman, can you just drive?
金刚
king kong!
嗨，我不是金刚
l'm not king kong!
不是金刚
lf you're not,
怎么会摔得这么美呢？
how come you feel so nice?
那倒是，不过我现在叫周围发
You're right! But l'm now called Ever Rich.
哦！上车吧发哥
Get on! Rich boy!
你想约我兜风？
Taking me for a ride?
今天时间太仓促了
l'm busy today.
我约了人谈生意
l've a meeting.
是不是这两个？
Are they...
是啊
Yes!
再见
Goodbye!
你把我当司机？
You're treating me like a driver?
我又不是母老虎，有什么好怕的？
Come sit beside me. Are you afraid of me?
我长这么大都没怕过
Afraid of you? l'm afraid of nothing!
不认识你就被你吓死
Those who don't know you will be scared to death by you.
认识你就被你笑死
Those who know you will laugh to death!
不可能的
lt's impossible,
我那来时间做这么多事？
we don't have time for this!
当然不可能了，以你现在这种状况
Of course! lmpossible, judging from your look now,
走路都会倒着走
so down and out.
你说什么？
What did you say?
是[新最佳拍档]  ，我跟我老弟做的
lt's done by the New Aces, me and my brother.
我们旧最佳拍档还没死呢
We, the Old Aces, are still around,
你们新的那里蹦出来呢？
how can you people beat us?
长江后浪推前浪
lt's time for you to retire!
一代新人葬旧人，拜拜
The new buries the old.
你干什么？
What do you want?
你知道秦始皇兵马俑最值钱是什么？
Do you know what's the most valuable thing in the Terracotta Army?
什么？兵马俑每一样都值钱
Every single piece is precious!
谁知道你说那件？
How would l know what you're talking about?
秦皇宝剑
lt's the sword!
给我再看一眼吧
Let me take a look again.
假的
lt's fake!
过份，我全都是真的
Fake? They're all real!
小姐，你误会了
You misunderstand.
我是说宝剑是假的！
l said the sword is fake!
什么？
What?
凭你的三脚猫功夫
You? No way!
怎么可能会偷到真的呢？
How can you get the real one?
小白痴一个
You stupid fool!
站住！
Don't go!
刚才你说三脚猫功夫 是说我没本事？
You just said l was not good enough, right?
是呀
Right!
我跟你比试一下
l'll fight with you!
比试？
With me?
不错
Yes!
我让你先动手
You take the first punch.
你打吧
Come on!
你叫我打你哪儿？
Where do you want me to hit?
你不打，我打
lf you don't move, l will!
来真的啊？玩够了，我不打女人的
Are you serious? But l don't hit women!
你认输了吧
You concede?
我认输？刚刚我才让了两个女人
Concede? l've just let off two women.
真要比的话，不用身体接触我就比
Let's fight without touching each other!
好主意
Good idea!
我定时间
l choose the time.
地点我定
l choose the place.
现在
Now!
那边
There!
来来…
Come on...
你不上来，在干什么？
What are you doing? Are you afraid?
厉不厉害？
Am l not great?
三年不练，功力犹存
Though l haven't practised for 3 years, l'm still strong!
阿Sir
Sir!
他像不像偷兵马俑的金刚？
Does he look like that king kong who stole the Terracotta Army?
你是不是偷兵马俑的金刚？
Are you that king kong who stole the Terracotta Army?
你有什么证据？
Do you have any evidence?
报纸都登出来了
lt is in the papers.
报纸写的你也相信？
You believe the papers?
我们怎样？
How is it now?
问他叫什么
Ask him his name.
你是谁？是不是金刚？
Who are you? Are you king kong?
下来，把你的身份证给我看看
Come on down. Let me see your lD card.
你们要看我身分证吗？
You want to see my l.D.?
我还以为你们在看我作秀哩！
l thought you want to see my show!
我上去拿给你们
l am now going up to get it for you.
他好像是金刚
He seems to be king kong!
我们上去
Let's go up.
他想逃跑
He's getting away.
别担心
He can't escape!
喂，华叔在吗？
Hello, Uncle Wah please.
喂，华叔，我是金刚
Uncle Wah, this is king kong.
怎么那么多人找我麻烦？
Why are so many people bringing me trouble?
我没有偷国宝啊！
l haven't stolen the national treasure!
会不会是光头佬跟别人做的？
ls it done by the Baldy and others?
光头佬现在在哪？
Where has the Baldy gone to?
华叔，香港是不是陆沉了？
Uncle Wah, is Hong kong sinking?
碰！开杠
Hold it! l have fours!
红中
Red Dragon.
碰！
Hold it.
红中你都敢打？大三元
You dare throw a ''Red Dragon''? A big win!
赢死你呀！给钱…
Pay me, pay me!
表舅
Uncle!
臭丫头，早点出声嘛
You little devil. Why didn't you speak up earlier?
我早出声你就早跳下去嘛
lf l spoke up earlier, you'd jump earlier.
表舅，别在我面前装傻了
Uncle, don't pretend to be stupid.
其实你比谁都精
You are smarter than anyone else.
我长得很精吗？
Do l look smart?
毛巾呢？
Where is the towel?
后面
At the back.
大家都是亲戚，何必做戏呢？
We are relatives, why bother to pretend?
我不会去告密的
l won't tell the police.
刚刚你说什么？
What are you saying?
没什么，报纸登得那么大
Nothing! l read the big headlines in the papers.
最佳拍档涉嫌夜盗国宝，厉害呀
The Aces are suspected of stealing a national treasure.
我会做这种有辱国体的事吗？
You think l did it?
一定是金刚这个小王八蛋
lt must be the bastard, king kong
跟别人一齐干的来陷害我
who did it to frame me.
存心要把我逼死嘛
He wants me dead.
你看，你看…
Look, girl!
这些人绝对不是来讨债的
They don't seem to be debt collectors.
那不就是来找我的
Then they are looking for me.
不找你找谁？
Who else could they be looking for?
找我干什么？
What do they want from me?
好像是为了兵马俑来的
l think they are coming for the Terracotta Army.
一定是金刚那个小王八蛋告的密
lt must be king kong who called the police
叫人来抓我的
to come and arrest me.
我走了
l have to go now.
你干嘛看着这个洞
Don't stare stupidly at this hole.
人家不就知道我在哪吗？
They'll know l'm hiding here!
还不走？
Go!
表舅，你慢慢跑路吧，我走了
Uncle, l'm leaving, have a good run!
再见
Bye!
你怎么了？小姐
What happened to you?
我牙齿痛
Toothache!
你牙齿痛还这么漂亮
Oh, you still look beautiful!
你一定是金刚的女朋友
You must be king kong's girlfriend!
还是个未知数哩
Not exactly!
那个小王八蛋有福不会享
That fool doesn't know his own luck!
他是色盲
He's colour-blind!
就是呀
Right!
对了，他在哪儿？
Where's he?
他被人追出去了，不…
They chased him out. Oh, no!
这里没有金刚
There's no king kong here,
这儿只有周围发
only ''Ever Rich''.
我知道
l know!
他最近有没有跟人家拍档？
Has he got any partners lately?
有，他的拍档可多着了
Yes! Many.
有没有做大买卖？
Any big business?
当然有啦
Of course!
他这个人最喜欢做大买卖了
He likes big deals.
他常常教我要Think big
He always teaches me to think big!
他还喜欢Talk big夸大其词哩
He always boasts.
他最近有没有说要害光头佬呢？
Has he ever talked against the ''Baldy''?
你知道我的意思？
You know who l'm talking about?
当然知道，从我上班那天开始
Of course! Right from my first day here,
他足足骂了他三年
he's been scolding this guy for 3 years.
骂了三年都不厌？
3 years! He's not tired?
不厌！就是这个死光头佬
No! This is the Baldy!
他还帮他编了首歌唱哩
He even wrote a song to curse the Baldy!
怎么个唱法？
Can you sing it?
很好听的，要不要我唱给你听？
lt's very nice, l'll sing it for you.
好呀，好呀，唱吧，唱…
Go ahead, sing...
渠衰格低庄，正光棍大王
He's disgusting.
无料当泵早收挡
He knows nothing, better retreat.
要将渠生ǎ再剁碎滚汤
Butcher him alive, and mince him for soup.
最衰拍档
The Worst Ace.
渠正系最衰拍档
He's really the Worst Ace.
永远系最衰拍档
Forever, the Worst Ace.
这么个唱法，难怪我足足倒霉了三年
Cursing me like this, no wonder l'm unlucky for 3 years.
小王八蛋怎么他还没有回来？
You bastard! ls he returning?
你说什么？原来真的是你
What did you say? lt's really you Baldy!
死光头佬，你把金刚害成这个样子
lt's you who made king kong so poor!
我憎恨你了，你走…你走…
l hate you most, you get lost, go away!
别打呀，别打…
Stop it! Stop it!
欢迎！是不是想投资呀？
Hi, are you looking for investment advice?
抓他
lt's him!
你们干什么？
What are you doing?
对不起
Excuse me!
老外打中国功夫
Chinese kung-Fu!
你们够了，为什么在这里打架？
Have you finished? Why do you fight here?
要打就出去打
Fight outside!
还不走，我报警！
lf not, l'll call the police!
臭丫头，不关你的事，别动
Bastard, none of your business. Don't move!
Deborah，你怎么了？
Deborah, what happened?
鬼打鬼，真好玩！
They're fighting each other, great!
偷秦王宝剑？真笑死人！
Steal the Emperor's sword? lt's crazy!
现在全世界都用机关枪了
Everybody uses guns now.
我要把剑有屁用？
What can l do with that precious sword?
这种无聊的事，只有金刚才做的
lt must be that rascal king kong who did it.
把他抓回来问个清楚，他最怕我的
Why don't you ask him?
他一见到我，两腿发软
He's terrified of me!
我折磨折磨他，他什么都招
Bring him here, let me make him suffer.
好啊
Good!
你们干什么？
What are you doing?
金刚？好久不见了
king kong? Long time no see!
你怎么会沦落成这样呢？
How come you're in such a state?
你活该！没事给我作首歌 骂了我三年
How dare you write a song to curse me for 3 years?
你还串通了别人去抢劫？
You committed a crime with others.
报纸都登出来了
lt's on the front page!
闭上你的乌鸦嘴
Shut up!
冻就冻吧，还死撑！
Admit it! Why suffer?
你们两个说够了没有？
Have you two finished?
秦皇宝剑藏在那儿？
Where's the sword?
我有了，我有了…好办法，好办法！
l got it! l have an idea!
你们这样逼他是没有用的
lt's useless to treat him like this.
他会这个九阳二指神功 还会梦见周公
He knows Tai-Chi, and Nina Ricci.
只要剥光了他的衣服
lf you take off his clothes,
他不死也半条命了
he will become dead meat.
别动
Don't move!
你们干什么？
What are you doing?
都冻僵了，起不来了！
l'm stone cold, l can't struggle!
我自己来吧
Let me do it myself.
这招高吧？
ls it a good idea?
Albert先生，你知不知道自古以来
Mr. Albert, l looked through Chinese History,
所有的汉奸都不得好死的？
none of the traitors end up well!
我也没见过自己的拍档见利忘义
l've never seen partners
出卖朋友…会有好下场的！
who betray their friends end up well!
天啊！为什么会让我认识这个光头佬？
Oh God! Why did you let me know this Baldy?
你自己倒霉，何必拖我下水呢？
Why did you pass your bad luck to me?
跟你拍档多久，我便衰多久
l've been suffering since we're partners.
我要点神功来唬唬老外
The Tai Chi l just demonstrated is only to divert the foreigners.
你也要拆穿我
And you want to spoil it!
你要说清楚
What did you say?
是谁把谁拖下水的
Who's dragged down who?
你偷东西可不承认，你还…
You won't admit that you stole. You...
吵够了没有？
Quiet!
你们两别再噜嗦了
No more pretence, two of you!
秦皇剑到底在哪？快说
Where's the Emperor's sword? Out with it!
闭嘴
Hold your tongue!
我们的事我们自己解决
We'll settle our own matters!
不用你来插嘴
lt's none of your business.
我们不会让外人看笑话的
We won't lose face in public.
金刚哦！
Right, king kong?
就是呀！
Right!
这几年来
These few years...
别被人家看扁了
Don't lose face in front of others.
这几年来，我可想死你了
These few years, l've always been thinking of you!
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
我没事
l'm fine!
难得今天跟你在雪地相逢
Meeting brother Baldy here today,
我们可以慢慢解决 我们这么多年的恩恩怨怨了
we can settle everything between us.
不是恩怨，是仇怨！
Not for gratitude, but for revenge.
咱们两没有什么好说的
There is no gratitude between us.
等他们一出去，我们得好好检讨
Once they leave, we should think over
我们最佳拍档这几年来的成败得失
the Aces' successes and failures!
我们和平友善的解决这个问题
Settle this problem amicably.
一定友善，我们是
Very amicably, because we're
最佳拍档！
The Aces!
不服气吗？
How is it?
有种！我最佩服讲义气的人
Good! l admire those real friends!
我先看到的
l saw it first!
谁打我？
Who hit me?
你这个小王八蛋！是我先看到的
You little dummy, l saw it first!
放手！  是我先看到的！
-Hands off! -lt's mine, l saw it first!
你争什么？
What are you doing?
就是，是我先看到的，你给我穿
l saw it first, so l should wear it!
给我穿  我穿
-Give it to me... -it's mine...
我撞死你
l'll run you over!
你有老婆孩子，你先穿吧！别着凉
You've a wife and child, you put it on. Health is important!
好…好呀！
Ok...
你们两真是患难见真情
You two are real good friends.
这还用说？
Needless to say!
快还我吧
Give it to me!
还什么还？
Give you what?
你不要硬抢呀
Snatch?
看你脱不脱
Take it off!
冻死我了
lt's freezing.
你拿过来吧
Give it to me!
再来一点…
A little more!
好冻呀，你好残忍！
l'm freezing. You're so cruel!
好暖呀！
lt's warm!
你喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
喜欢
Yeah!
宝剑藏在那？
Where's that precious sword?
如果再不说，我们便再来一次
We'll do it again if you insist keep your mouth shut.
解了冻再结冻
Freeze and then defrost again!
我们真的不知道，你叫我怎么说呢？
How can l tell you when l don't know?
放我下来…我说我说…我说…
Please put me down. l'll tell you...
放下来
Put them down!
老大，我冻得牙齿都打颤了
Big brother, it's freezing.
你叫我们怎么说？
What do you want me to say?
我穿了衣服才能说呀  是呀
-Let's get our clothes on first! -Yeah!
把衣服给他们
Give them back their clothes.
希望你们这一次最好说真话
l hope you tell the truth this time.
一定是真的，我来告诉你
Certainly! l came to tell you!
我有悄悄话跟你大哥说，谢谢
l've a big gift for your big brother!
我即刻回来
l'll be right back.
大哥，大哥大，大姐头
Big brother, big big brother, big big big sister.
我已经不是以前的那个金刚了
l, king kong, am different now.
我现在是金融界巨子，大商家
l'm now doing well in finance and commerce.
怎么可能偷东西呢？
Do l still need to steal?
我可不是光头佬
l'm not like Brother Baldy.
欠了钱便跑路！还有…
Old-fashioned and hiding from debts.
我是从不出卖朋友的
Also, l never betray friends.
不过我现在告诉你一个秘密
But l have to tell you a secret now.
宝剑是光头佬和一个女孩子偷的
That sword was stolen by Brother Baldy and a girl.
刚才在冰库里，他还告诉我收藏的地方
He even told me where he hid the sword.
你这个小王八蛋
You bastard,
你在背后说我坏话
talking behind my back?
谁说你坏话？
What did l say?
你以为我不记仇？岂有此理
Do you think l don't know? How dare you?
光头佬，快走！
Go! Brother Baldy!
追，去抓他们
Get them, get those idiots.
跳吧
Jump!
没事哩，没摔死！
lt's safe. You won't die!
不过我们在公车顶上
But we are on top of the bus!
当然在公车才叫你跳
l knew we were landing on the bus top.
算准时间的
Perfect timing.
快坐下，要开车了
Come on, sit down. The bus is moving.
真好！
lt's great.
每次出事都是我救你
l have to rescue you every time!
再见…又让你出风头了
Goodbye... You're great this time.
我们怎下车？
How shall we get off?
你会不会单杠？
Do you know how to play horizontal bar?
不会
No!
来
Come on!
你们在这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
快去借个电话打给华叔
Let's call Uncle Wah.
去啦，快点！
Go! Hurry!
是…打给华叔
Yes... Call Uncle Wah.
快点啊！
Quick!
会议室
Conference Room.
华叔在吗？
Uncle Wah, please answer the phone.
光头佬找他
lt's Brother Baldy.
你说我不在
Tell him l'm not in.
Tell him l'm not in, l'm not...
说我上厕所
Tell him l'm in the toilet.
他在，接过来吧
He's here! Put the line through here please!
华叔
Uncle Wah!
华叔呀，兵马俑是谁…  我来吧
-Uncle Wah, who did it... -Let me!
喂，华叔，我是金刚
Uncle Wah, l am king kong.
我们被人假扮最佳拍档 害得好惨！
Someone had framed us by stealing the national treasure.
次次我们有祸都是你帮我们搞定
We are in deep trouble now.
麻烦你找交通部帮忙
Please check with the Transport Dept.
查查车子在那里…
to see where the car is.
我知道
l know.
CC109的车停在那里？
Where is CC109 parked?
阿弟，你实在没用
Ben, you're just unbelievable.
香港那么小，也找不到光头佬
Hk is such a small place but you can't find Baldy.
记着，找到他一定要好好修理他
Remember, we have to teach him a good lesson when we find him.
阿弟，你真行！千万别让他动
Ben, Bravo! Don't let him move!
他的拍档一定也在附近
His partner must be around.
你说对了
You're right!
小姐，请上车吧
Miss, get on!
行了，我…
Okay, l will...
你用不着放电了
lt's no use flirting with me.
我现在是六根清净
l'm not interested at all.
简直好像是同性恋，不…不是
l'm rather feminine now.
我以前是好色了一点
l used to be a Lothario
不过现在对爱情看得很淡了
Now l'm very blase about love.
我以前是身经百战…
After going through hundreds of battles.
钥匙
key!
披荆斩棘、豺狼当道 民不聊生、处变不惊…
Up to heaven, down to earth... Sweet, sour, hot, spicy... Every taste.
上车！  你脱了衣服我也不怕
Let's get on!
就算你是玛丽莲梦露，也没用…
Not even if you were Marilyn Monroe!
不要动
Don't move!
枪不要指着我，你指着她嘛
Don't point it at me, point at her!
还没电到你，你就语无论次了
She hasn't moved on you, but you're already insane!
她有电到啊！
She has!
不要动，坐好
Don't move! Sit tight!
不要再发电了，听见了没有？
Stop flirting, you!
长江后浪推前浪，对嘛？
New talent will wash over old ones, right?
到了渔场就知道谁推谁了
You'll know who washes who when you go to the fish farm.
谁怕谁呀？
Who's scared of who now?
你们这两个老兔子 能玩什么花招来呀？
You two old bastards, what's up your sleeves?
对呀！你们两个有什么了不起？
Right! You two aren't so great!
一个是假精明，一个是真笨蛋
One is too smart, one is too stupid.
加起来，只能演滑稽秀
Added together, you're a joke!
闭嘴，满嘴放屁
Enough! Too much talking!
开车
Let's go!
我还没耍够你，老王八蛋
We haven't had enough fun with you. Damn you!
骂我王八蛋？
Damn me?
小心开车，他们死了没关系 我们两个的命要紧
Hey! Watch out. Our lives are more precious than theirs.
我们两是最佳拍档
We're The Aces!
你到底是帮他还是帮我？
Are you on my side or theirs?
当然是帮我们
Ours, of course!
你这种臭光头，谁帮你谁倒霉
Baldy, you always bring bad luck to your partner.
你不要动手动脚
Don't touch me.
放手，我最恨人家骂我光头
Hands off! l hate people calling me Baldy.
放手…小王八蛋
Damn you.
光头佬，不要打了…小心开车
Baldy! Hands off!
臭光头…我揍死你…
Baldy, stop. Sit down!
不要打了…看着前面
Don't fight!
你搞什么，别动手动脚
You're so rude! Don't move!
怎会这样子的
Why?
快点站上去平衡车子
Try balancing the car with your body!
我站不起来
l can't stand up!
站不上去也得站，快点 后一点，后一点…
Try! Hurry up!
受不了你，好危险呀
lt's dangerous.
又来了…  看着呀…
Oh, it comes again!
妈的！你怎会让他们跑了？
Damn! How could you let them get away?
老板，现在已经没有办法了
Boss, we can't do anything now.
我们最好带全部的兵马俑 立刻离开香港
We better leave Hk with the Terracotta Army.
我要把宝剑拿回来
l want the Chinese Excalibur back.
老板，很危险的
Boss, it's very dangerous.
怎会危险，没有人知道我们在这儿
Why? No one knows our location.
那两个混蛋把宝剑抢走
But having those 2 steal the Excalibur from under our nose.
害我们丢人，以后怎么出来混？
How can l face the others?
快把剑找回来
l want the sword back.
姐姐，姐…你在那里？
Sis, where are you?
姐姐…
Sis...
阿弟，你没事吧？
Ben, are you alright?
我们被人绑起来了
We're tied up.
又是你们这两个老兔子！
lt's you two bastards again!
玻璃棺材，怎样跟他玩
Glass coffin, how do we deal with her?
好波，够养眼
Good figure, attractive.
弹下弹下好抢眼
Up and down, very attractive!
就怕你们抓到 他们也拿我们没办法！
l'm afraid you won't know how to trick us even if you catch us.
就是呀
Right!
看他们两个笨样子 也玩不出什么花样来
l believe they can't do anything.
姐姐你看，这下面好多鱼啊 每条鱼都好大
Of course! You see, Sis. There're many fishes. All of them are big!
对呀！可以拿出来做Sasime
Right! Like the sashimi we ate in Japan!
对呀
Right!
怎么会这样子的？
How come?
阿弟，不用怕，镇定点
Ben, don't be afraid. Calm down.
你们玩够了没有？
Have you people had enough?
玩够了没有？游戏还没有开始哩
Enough? The game hasn't started!
你够了？
Alright!
小王八蛋，你为什么要害我们？
Bastard, why did you frame us?
我翻脸了
l'm furious.
翻脸？
Furious?
你干嘛打我？
Why did you hit me?
不要咬我，好痛呀
lt hurts...
救命呀
Help!
阿弟，不要怕，镇定点
Ben, be calm!
够了，快把我们解开
Have you people had enough? Let us go!
不要…
No...
你看看，她翻脸了
That one is getting furious too!
跟她玩玩吧  好啊
-Time to play with her! -Ok!
姐姐…
Sis... Are you alright?
我说了…
l confess.
说了
lt's relaxing!
快点说
Confess now!
阿弟，你告诉他们吧 我说他们相信的
Ben, you tell them. They don't believe me.
女孩子说的话我最信的
No, l want the pretty lady to say it!
宝剑藏在那里？
Where's the precious sword?
人在剑在，人亡剑亡
The sword is where the man is.
手中无剑，心中有剑
No sword in hand, it exists in the heart.
两位大侠，西门吹风
Good! Two swordsmen!
吹你妈的头，你们到底说不说？
Are you going to confess or not?
把我们放了我才说，快点啊
After you untie us, we confess.
好，把他们先放了
Alright! Untie them first.
小王八蛋，怎么放呢？
How?
这招是你想的，你该知道怎样做的
You planned this, you should know how to untie them!
我不会
No, l don't!
你一辈子都这样，头大没脑
You always like this!
有了头就没有尾！
You never know how to wrap things up.
我们一人站一边 让板子平衡就行了
Let's each go to one end to get balance and then untie the rope, that's it?
你说得对，看看我英雄救美
Right! Let me, the hero, rescue the beauty.
你们两个笨蛋小心点，小心呀
You two be careful! Watch out!
放心吧，我们最佳拍档办事从没出过错
Take it easy! The Aces never fail!
小心点
Calm down!
你太重了，快过去啊
lt's too heavy on my side, go to the other side.
不要过来
Don't come over!
快过去啊
Go back!
不要过来
Don't come over!
叫什么？是我被鱼咬，又不是你
Quiet! l've been bitten by the fish not you!
我的手指甲弄伤了
l hurt my finger nail.
别那么大声啊？我这是硬撑着
Lower your voice, l'm also suffering.
别让人看扁了
Don't lose face in front of others.
最差劲是你，想这种怪招
Damn you! How could you think this up?
害人又害已
Hurts both yourself and others.
只有智商零蛋才想得出这种烂招
Only idiots can come up with this!
对不对？
Right?
就是
Right!
都是你，你非要换边，它就不平衡了
Did you not say each one controls one side?
那你不早说，现在说有个屁用？
Why didn't you speak up? l thought everything's fine.
怪不得金刚说跟他拍档会倒霉一辈子
No wonder king kong says Baldy brings bad luck!
对呀
Right!
他们两个说得很对
They seem to be right!
对你妈个头，每次都是我
Bullshit! l always start right,
把开头弄得好好的 最后给你弄砸了
but you mess things up!
放屁，少胡说！
What? Think before you speak!
谁胡说？你还记不记得
You disagree? Had you not pretended
三年前要不是你假仁慈
to be kind 3 years ago,
我们也不会倒霉到现在！对吧？
we wouldn't be in this state, right?
对！还是你说得对
That's true!
少煽风点火，宝剑在那？快说
What are you two up to? Where's the sword?
远在天边，近在眼前
Far away as in heaven, near by as in front of you.
远在天边？
Far away as in heaven?
近在眼前？一定在她姐姐身上
Near by? lt's must be with his sister!
剥光她的衣服搜身
Take off her clothes and search!
来
Right, take them off!
别趁机揩油呀，走开，我说了
Don't take advantage on her!
你说呀
Come on! Tell us!
先放开我们
Untie me first!
你再乱来我便把你姐姐扔下水
Don't play games or l'll throw your sister into the sea.
对呀！我就剥光她的衣服
Right! Let me take off her clothes.
阿弟
Ben!
小王八蛋，你不老实，我自己来
You're up to no good, l'll do it.
真的有
The sword is here!
还不救他
Go and help him.
小弟弟全都没了
l've lost everything!
姐姐，这招妙吧
Sis, you're great!
那还用说，快把它拉出来吧 不然就没了
Of course! Go help him or... We're finished.
把肌肉放松啊
Relax.
怎么放呀？放不松呀
How? l can't.
再见…
Goodbye!
为什么会这样？
What happened?
阿弟…
How come? Ben...
有鲨鱼呀！快
Sharks!
快点
Hurry up!
快救我！救命呀…
Help me! Please help me...
怎么回事？
What happened?
接着
Hold it!
往前游
Go on!
把手给我
Give me your hand!
上来
Get up!
干什么？什么事？
What happened?
怎么出海了？
Why are we out at sea?
这些人什么来头？
Who are they?
不像是警察
They don't look like cops.
什么人？
Who are you?
你们是干什么的？
What do you want?
公安
National Security!
你们想怎么样？
What do you want?
你们要把我们拉到那儿去？
Where are you taking us?
当然是去厦门
Xiamen, of course!
我看是去江门
l thought it was Jiangmen.
对了
Right!
你这样做是违反香港人的自由权
You're acting against Hk's human rights.
我们要到联合国告你们
l'll report you to the United Nations.
悉随尊便！高兴的话 就跳进海里游上岸吧
Do what you like! You can jump and swim ashore!
海里这么多鲨鱼，我们怎跳？
But how, there're so many sharks?
随便找一个跳下去喂饱它不就行了吗？
One of you go feed the sharks first!
你最肥，你跳下去最好了
You have more flesh, you jump first!
叫你姐姐跳
Ask your sis to jump first!
你说什么？
You're crazy!
鲨鱼又不是哺乳的
Sharks don't breast feed!
就是呀
Right!
你别跟他胡扯
Stop kidding!
走…快点…
Go...
走快一点…走…快点…
走…走啊！
Go... Quick!
快走…
Go... Go...
香港来的？
From Hong kong?
自己人！  他知道
Oh, fellows from home. He knows.
干什么？
What are you doing?
同志…不好意思，不好意思…
Sir... l'm sorry, excuse me.
他们是我最好的朋友
We're friends.
我跟他们是死党，死党，没问题！
Everything will be fine!
不好意思…
l'm sorry...
有没有烟？
Do you have any cigarette?
没有
No!
酒呢？
Wine?
没有
No!
那进来混个屁？
How can you come here?
什么罪？什么罪？
What crime did you commit?
你犯了什么罪了？
How about you? What have you done?
我？嫖客
Me? Whoremongering!
你这个样子回香港怎么见人？
How can you go home with the words on your forehead?
回到香港整整容就行了
l can go for plastic surgery!
有没有钱？
You got money?
没有
No!
一点利用价值都没有
You're useless!
少废话，走！走…
Don't bullshit! Go!
坦白，坦白呀！坦白从宽！
Be honest! Honesty is most important!
我无自由，我失自由 老子我今天也被囚禁
No freedom, l lost freedom!
快呀快，快一点
Hurry up, be quick!
你干什么？
Are you jumping queue?
到后面排队！去
Line up at the back! Go!
姐姐
Sis!
抢什么？
What are you pushing for?
谢谢…
Thanks...
多给一点嘛！
Some more please!
就这么多
That's all, go!
快走，快…快
Be quick, hurry up!
快走
Damn you, go, quick!
姐姐，你怕什么嘛？
Sis, don't be afraid.
小王八蛋，都是你不好…
Bastard, if not for you, we wouldn't end up like this. Damn you.
死光头，想打架吗？
You wanna fight?
你们别吵了，烦死我了
Please... Please stop arguing!
都什么时候了，还狗咬狗？
You wanna die?
要互相帮助嘛
Don't you think we should find a way to get out together?
谢谢班长
Sir...
快点吃，杀人王等着你
The killer is waiting for you.
是…
Yes...
他怎么吃得那么好？
Why do you have such a good meal?
你们犯了什么罪？
What have you done?
盗国宝
We've stolen a national treasure.
盗国宝？
Stolen a national treasure?
我嫖个妓等了两年才吃到这一顿
Because of a whore, l was sentenced to death 2 years ago.
你们很快就吃到了！盗国宝
You'll get yours soon.
这一顿是你最后的晚餐？
ls this your last supper?
是呀，吃饱了这一顿 就要去见杀人王
Yes, l've to see The killer after the dinner
挑子弹了
to buy bullets.
这一顿饭不用花钱，政府送的
This last supper is free of charge.
枪毙那颗子弹，就要自己出钱买
But you have to pay for the bullet for execution.
你们有没有钱？
Do you have money?
过来，我教你们怎么挑子弹
Come, let me teach you how to choose bullets.
很快就轮到你们了
lt will be your turn soon.
这是步枪子弹，尖头的 前面进，后面出
This is a rifle bullet, pointed. Once fired, in from front, out from back.
可是一枪是死不了，要两枪
One shot doesn't work, so you need two.
这可不同了，全都是铁沙的
This one is different.
一开枪，立即飞过去
Once you shoot, the shot spreads out.
立刻变成蜜蜂窝了，死得很难看
lt's horrible!
这个不要买，太贵了
Don't buy these, too expensive!
要买就买一整排，满身枪眼 不好玩
You'll get bullet holes all over your body if you pick this one.
这些圆头的，小洞进，大洞出
This is round-headed.
打进去，肠子都跑出来了
Once you get shot, the intestines fall out.
子弹粘在骨头上，还得用刀刮！
The bullet sticks onto bones!
恐怖
Horrible too!
她怎么了？
What happened to her?
恶心得想吐！
Can't stand it!
这一颗厉害，我建议买这一颗
This one is powerful! l suggest you buy this!
短小精悍，一枪中心脏，好爽
You won't feel a thing.
同志，这一颗多少钱？
Hi pal, how much is this?
五毛钱
Fifty cents.
五毛钱？我只有五毛钱 存了两年了
Fifty cents. Here you are. l've saved for 2 years.
你在这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
买子弹
Buying bullets.
出去
Go out!
是
Yes sir!
我走了，他问什么都要坦白呀
l'm leaving. Answer him truthfully!
早点[砰]比晚点[砰]好啊
Better to be shot earlier than later.
坐
Sit.
知不知道你们犯了什么罪？
Do you know what your crime is?
不知道？
No, l don't!
最高领导人，我们两个没有罪
Officer, we're innocent.
他们两个才有罪！
They're the guilty ones.
谁说你们没有罪 没罪怎么会进来？
You're innocent? Why are you here then?
你们再说一遍
You have one more chance.
叫他说
Let him tell the truth.
自己说，不是，你们说啊
Come on! Tell them the truth.
我们有罪
We're guilty.
什么罪？
For what?
盗国宝
Stealing the country's treasure.
好，你们谁盗国宝？
Fine! Who did it?
他
He did!
秦皇宝剑从你们那里找出来的
The precious sword was found in your place.
兵马俑也一定是你们偷的
The Terracotta Army must be stolen by you too!
你们要负责把他们找回来
You must bring it back right away!
关我什么事？我们没有偷啊
-We didn't steal the treasure. -That has nothing to do with us.
是他们偷的！  不是我们偷的
-lt's stolen by them. -No.
买子弹
Buy bullets.
姐姐
Sis!
同志，我才嫖了一次妓便砰死我
Buddy, l've only whoremongered once. l shouldn't be sentenced!
早知道我便多嫖几次！
lf l knew it, l should have done more!
你在那干嘛？
What are you doing here?
枪毙，难道是做秀？
Being executed, do you think l'm giving a show?
同志呀，求求你枪法准一点
Buddy! Please make it a clean shot.
打中这颗星的下面
Shoot beneath the star, let me die in one shot!
求求你一枪把我解决算了
Please!
很快就轮到你们四个了
Hey! lt's your turn soon!
预备，开枪
Ready, set!
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
枪法怎么那么烂？
Why is your aim so bad?
你那一颗子弹，我不认账的
Don't count on me for the second bullet.
别吹了，烦死了
Stop it. lt's disturbing!
光头佬，我们认识多久了？
Baldy, how long have we known each other?
我认识你多久便多久了
For as long as we knew each other.
有那么久了
So long!
你哭什么啊？
Why are you crying?
我绿帽子带定了！
l'll be a victim of infidelity!
为什么？
Why?
我被人毙了以后 我老婆一定带着小光头改嫁
lf l die, my wife will surely marry again.
那我不就戴绿帽子了吗？
l'll suffer infidelity!
不会的
No!
为什么不会？要是倒过来
Why not? lf my wife dies,
我老婆死了，我一定会去找别人
l'd certainly marry another woman!
不要胡思乱想了，先喝一杯
Don't think like that! Let's have a drink.
不要这样嘛 我们是不是最佳拍档？
Come on! Aren't we The Aces?
是，是最佳拍档
Yes, The Aces!
那你还生不生我的气？
You're not mad at me any more?
我那有时间去生你气
l prefer to save my breath.
光头佬，我们永远都是最佳拍档
Brother Baldy, we're the Best Aces Forever!
最佳拍档要带绿帽子的
The Best Ace has to suffer infidelity!
阿弟
Ben!
你看他们这么可怜 我们还是认了吧，好不好？
l'm so touched! Let's tell the truth, okay?
不要哭了，宝剑是我们偷的
Don't cry. The precious sword is stolen by us!
你跟我们说有个屁用
lt's no use confessing to us!
你去跟杀人王说才有用嘛
You have to tell The killer.
明天我们两个认了就是了
l'll go and tell him tomorrow!
两个人死总比四个人死好
We shouldn't drag you two down too.
何况你还有老婆孩子
Especially you. You have a family.
我们也没想到会变成这样
We never thought we'd end up like this.
你们为什么要假装我们去偷宝剑？
Why did you do it?
你们还记不记得那个泰国人？
Do you remember that Thai?
是他付钱叫我们陷害你们的
He paid us to get you in trouble.
就是那个混蛋？
The same Thai?
我们也知道他是个国际大混蛋
We know he's an asshole.
不过拿人钱财，替人消灾 那有什么办法呢？
But we had to fulfil our obligations.
钱不代表一切
Money is not everything.
那你错了，你没有穷过
You're wrong! You've never been poor!
我天天被人讨债，钱就代表一切！
l'm always in debt. To me, money is everything.
反正，我们明天把所有事情告诉杀人王
Anyway, we'll tell The killer everything tomorrow.
到时候你们就没事了
You'll soon be free.
不错，一人做事一人当
Right, we'll admit what we've done!
好，你们够义气
Good! You're real good friends.
你们还不算坏得没救
At least you're willing to confess.
这样吧，趁你们还没有死之前
Come on. Let's make friends
我们大家交个朋友
before you die.
以后我们会替你们上香的
We'll burn you incense sticks.
对，来干一杯  来
Right! Come on, let's toast! Let's toast!
干就干吧！来
Come on...
来，友谊万岁！    万岁
To Friendship!
人生于世上有几个知已
How many confidantes do we get in life?
多少友谊能长存
How long can friendships last?
今日别离共你双双两握手
Today we temporarily part,
友谊常在你我心里
Friendship is inside my heart forever.
今天且有暂别
Today we temporarily part,
他朝也定能聚首
we'll meet again.
纵使不能会面
Even we won't meet again,
始终也是朋友
we're still friends!
干
Cheers!
说有万里山
Even far away,
隔阻两地情
Amid obstacles,
带他们出来
Get them out.
鬼呀！
Ghosts.
我不是鬼
l'm not a ghost!
是这两位同志请我来这作一场监狱秀
lt's the 2 officers who asked me to pretend.
吓吓你们的！真不好意思
You're scared, l'm sorry!
谢谢…混饭吃嘛
Thank you! Just making a living.
我要赶飞机回香港
l'm in a hurry to catch the flight back to Hk!
我演得好不好？
Did l do well?
真坏
Terrible!
起码骗到你们
At least l fooled you!
几位请坐，不要客气
Have a seat, please.
很抱歉
l'm sorry.
我们请这么多人来演这场监狱风云
We just want you to work with us,
目的是希望你们合作
so we arranged such an act.
我们已经查清楚了
We know The Terracotta Army
兵马俑是白手套他们抢去的
was stolen by the White Gloves.
现在还在香港
They're still in Hong kong.
希望你们新旧最佳拍档 帮我们把国宝抢回来
l hope you old and new Aces can help us to get back the treasures.
可以，这个没问题
No problem at all.
对呀，男儿为国家…
lt's our obligation...
男儿为国家也是应该的
lt's our duty to our country.
不过我们现在已经改行做生意了
Unfortunately, we're businessmen now.
是呀，我们三年没有练功
Right... We haven't practised for 3 years.
技术已经不灵了！对吗？
We're not in peak form.
对对！所以我们也跟他们 改行做生意了
Right... We are also learning business from them.
是的
Yes.
你们真的不肯合作，不要耍花招
You really don't want to cooperate?
否则我就不客气
l don't want to be rude!
好了好了！大家冷静一点
Alright, let's calm down.
你们几位真的不肯帮忙？
You really don't want to cooperate?
中国有十亿人，为什么要我们帮忙？
China has a billion people, why us?
对呀！
Why?
你们是不肯合作了？
You refuse?
我们不想以国家的名义
Our government wants to keep this case
来处理这件事
low profile.
如果你们不肯帮忙
You may not want to get involved,
白手套也会来找你们
but the White Gloves will come after you anyway.
不要跟他们废话
Don't mess around with them.
我看干脆… 怎么样？
l think we better... How did it go?
他们说什么？
What did they say?
好像是去劳改
Sounds like they want us in Brainwash Camp!
去那里？
Where?
不对，好像是枪毙
No, sounds like they want us executed!
枪毙？
Shoot us dead?
姐姐，别昏倒！答应他…
Sis, don't faint! Cooperate...
好了，没有问题，我们答应你们了
Alright! No problem. We promise you.
我们一定合作 帮你们把兵马俑抢回来的
We'll get the Terracotta Army back for you.
为了我们的成功干杯
A toast to our success!
恭喜你
Congratulations!
谢谢
Thanks!
为你们的诚意干杯
Let us toast to your sincerity!
诚意，诚意，干杯
Sincerity, cheers...
要完成这次光荣的任务
ln order to finish this glorious mission,
你们要一定要接受严格的体能训练
you have to undergo thorough physical training.
你们最拿手的是什么武器？
May l ask what arms you're good at?
废话，当然是枪！
Guns, of course!
我说手枪、机关枪啊
Hand gun, machine gun?
我习惯用点三五史密夫威尔逊 你们有吗？
l usually use 0.35 Smith & Wesson.
不是这枝，这只能耍花枪！
Not this ''chinese gun''!
你干脆给我枝烟枪嘛
You might as well give me a joystick!
这一次我们去抢的是兵马俑
This is the Terracotta Army,
不可以用现代武器
we can't use modern arms.
以免破坏了那批国宝
ln order not to destroy the treasure,
所以我们这一次要用古代兵器
we must use ancient arms this time.
绝对不可以用枪械
Absolutely no guns will be used.
你老实说，我们的敌人会不会用枪械？
Be frank, will our enemy use guns?
很有可能
Probably!
敌方很可能用飞机大炮
Our enemy will probably use planes and cannons!
而我们只可以用这种小花枪 别笑死人了！
How can we only have this rubbish?
喝杯咖啡去吧！  去啦
Let's go have some tea!
好，我请客  好啊
Fine, my treat.
你们要干什么？
What do you want?
小老弟，不是我不肯帮你
kid, not that we don't want to help you.
对呀，怎可用这种小孩玩具去拼命？
But how can we fight with only these?
小姐，这个只可以用来做做秀！
Miss, this is only something for shows.
对呀！这玩意还没列入奥运比赛项目
Right, this game is not in the Olympic Games programme yet.
西洋剑还差不多
A western sword might work.
就是，我看你们还是改用西洋剑吧
Maybe you should switch to a western sword.
改天我教你
l'll teach you some day.
先走了，喝茶
l gotta go!
姐姐，喝点什么？
What would you like to drink?
我喝这个
l'll drink this!
这里有四把西洋剑
There are four western swords.
你们四个如果赢了她这把中国剑
lf you defeat her,
我就让你们走
l'll let you go!
如果我是你们，我就会选中国武器
lf l were you, l'd choose Chinese arms.
当然选西洋剑啦
l choose the western sword.
我样样精通，不知道你们行不行
lt doesn't matter to me, how about you?
我是学校女子冠军
l was the girls' champion in school.
我也学过好几年
l've learnt for years.
我从前是海陆空总教练
l was the head coach of the Ghurkhas before.
从没听说过
l have never heard about it.
留点面子好不好？
Give me a little face!
总教练，我先跟她玩玩
l'll go first.
不能丢人啊
Watch out.
小心啊
Be careful.
等着瞧吧
Watch out.
你完蛋了
You finish.
让我来
Let me do it. Come on, come on...
你没气了？
Are you exhausted?
你认输了吧
Surrender, will you?
输了吧
She lost!
她输了，你说过我们打赢她就可以走的
You promised if we win, we could leave!
吕燕，你输了没有？
Lui Yin, do you concede?
我没输！
No!
你没事吧？
Are you alright?
她翻脸啊
She is furious!
看我的
Don't be scared, l am still here.
不要动，你输了，怎么样？
Not dead yet?
我们赢了，你还要再来
We win, do you want to try again?
我们赢了
We win.
拼死拼活的乱打一通
You fight without any skill.
你们没赢，剑还在我的手上
You have not won. The sword is still with me.
你自己输了，还发脾气？
You lost.
你一点体育精神都没有
You have to admit the truth.
对呀！要是来真的，你已经死了
Right! lf those are real swords, you're dead!
岂有此理！
Nonsense!
什么东西？真是的！
Such brutality!
我现在死了没有？
Am l a dead person now?
不服气，你再来
Do you concede?
我已经说了不玩
l don't want to play anymore.
她很拼命的
She fought with her life.
不错，这位小姐打架是不怕死的
Right, this girl fought with her life
因为她答应了国家
because she promised the country.
你们也答应过我帮我抢回兵马俑
You also promised to help me get the Terracotta Army!
你们出尔反尔，好
But now you're breaking your word.
你们可以走
You can leave now.
以后别让我听到最佳拍档这四个字！
Don't let me hear the words ''The Aces'' again.
算了，我们走，因为他们怕
Ok, we'll leave because they're chicken.
怕？我们会怕？
We're chicken?
唏唏呵呵！我未惊过
Hey hey oh oh, l'm never scared!
我细细个，已经好威猛事迹多多
l've done great deeds from an early age,
扮武松打虎打到只猎狗累低
Defeated even the hunting dogs.
班靓仔个个服我，叫我阿哥
The kids admired me and called me ''Big Brother''.
我未惊过
l've never been frightened.
有杀错没有放过
l'm merciless.
见靓女即上“My name is paul”
When l see a pretty girl, l'll say ''My name is Paul''.
撞正个妈打四百磅大肥婆
When l run into her 400 lbs mother
渠黎手秤住我
who holds me suddenly and forces me to Tango,
要我跳似火探戈，我未惊过
l've never been frightened.
谁没有错，跌倒多少遍再站起过
Who's never done wrong? Just pick yourself up again.
路径坎坷不叹奈何
Don't complain about failures or hardships.
用我双手乾坤转过
Use my hand to change my fate.
无论挫折有几多，我未惊过
No matter how many setbacks, l've never been frightened.
唏唏呵呵！我未惊过…
Hey hey oh oh, l'm never scared!
有你兴我，并肩一起抗逆境风波
Either you or me, two together against misfortunes.
面对世间一切那害怕又如何
Facing the world, afraid of nothing.
一起再次突破，再唱劲歌
Break through once again together, singing pop songs.
谁没有错？跌倒多少遍再站起过
Who's never done wrong? Just pick yourself up again.
路径坎坷不叹奈何
Don't complain about failures or hardships.
用我双手乾坤转过
Use my hand to change my fate.
无论挫折有几多，我未惊过！
No matter how many setbacks, l've never been frightened.
唏唏呵呵！我未惊过…
Hey hey oh oh, l'm never scared!
金刚…
king kong...
对不起，你来这儿干什么？
l'm sorry! What are you doing here?
华叔已经全都告诉我了
Uncle Wah has already told me all.
我把我爷爷的宝剑都给你带来了
l've even brought along my Grandpa's sword.
不用你帮我，你回公司去
You don't have to help me. Go back to the office.
可是公司都被砸烂了
Everything in the office is broken.
又来过了…
Again, again...
死丫头
You girl!
死光头佬
Damned Brother Baldy!
你来这干什么？  关你什么事？
-What are you doing here? -None of your business!
待会收拾你！来…
Brother Baldy... Come on...
剑有灵气？
The sword has powers?
我老爸说的，中国剑有剑气 剑术、剑击、剑道
Father said, ''A Chinese sword has its spirit'', sword skill, sword technique, sword mannerism.
练到最高境界还会成仙哩！
After you've been to the highest level, you'll be a God!
照你这么说，真是有剑仙
You're saying there's a sword God?
当然，还可以剑气伤人！
Yes. You can even hurt people with this spirit.
那岂不是可以放飞剑？
Can the sword fly too?
就像武侠片一样
Just like those in Cantonese movies?
你真是个大傻瓜
Silly!
为什么不相信我？
Why don't you believe me?
来
Come on!
还有，中国剑不可以弄湿的
Remember, a Chinese sword cannot get wet.
洗澡的时候就把它挂好
You've to hang it up when you bath.
要不然灵气就会跑掉的
Or else the power will be gone.
你相不相信我的话？
Do you believe me?
要听真的？
Do you want me to tell the truth?
当然听真的
Of course!
我才不相信
l don't believe it.
去你的…走呀…走…
Go to hell! Go... Quick.
别过来
Don't come over!
别过来…
停手
Stop!
退后
Step back!
带她走
Take her away.
路径坎坷不叹奈何
Don't complain about failures or hardships.
用我双手乾坤转过
Use my hand to change my fate.
无论挫折有几多，我未惊过！
No matter how many setbacks l've never been frightened.
阿弟
Ben!
光头佬，拜托你不要唱了
Brother Baldy, you sing very badly.
阿弟  干什么？干什么？
-Ben! -What?
你们懂不懂音乐？  姐姐！
-Do you two know how to sing? -Sis...
我唱歌你还说不好听
l sing terribly?
我同徐小凤有合唱过
l sang with pop singers!
干什么？
What's the matter?
你们到那儿去啊？
Where are you going?
老土
Old-fashioned!
笨点子
What a stupid idea!
寄简留剑
Leaving messages with a sword!
没想到白手套也有萧芳芳和陈宝珠
l can't imagine the White Gloves leaving a message in such an old-fashioned way.
这好像都是拉丁文？
Latin?
反过来念，傻瓜
The other way round! ldiot!
如要救小妹，快拿宝剑来赎人
lf you want to rescue the girl,
长洲码头等
bring the sword to Cheung Chau pier.
你们怎么知道的？
How do you know?
这张纸是透明的，笨！
lt's transparent, idiot!
聪明先生，请问下一步怎么办？
Mr. Clever, what's next?
当然是拿宝剑去救人！
Take the sword to save Ellen.
不错，找中国蓝波去借宝剑
Let's go to Chinese Rambo to borrow the sword.
你别想，他是冲动派掌门人
Are you crazy? He is so temperamental,
你真是没事找事！
lt will only make things worse.
那怎办？
Then what shall we do?
你们可以走了
You can leave now.
为什么？
Why?
我们已经被撤职了
We're fired.
中央认为我手段太极端
The government thought my methods too extreme,
所以把我革职了
so they fired me.
你们真的可以走了
l'm not kidding. You can go now.
那兵马俑怎么办？
How about the Terracotta Army?
国家会用外交关系拿回来的，没有问题
China will get them back through diplomatic channels.
有什么对不起的地方，请多多包涵
Please forgive what l did to you.
等等，我们算不算朋友？
Are we friends?
友谊万岁！
Friendship forever.
宝剑借来用一用，行不行？
May l use your sword? Come on!
你说友谊万岁的嘛
You said friendship forever!
万万岁
Ever and ever!
有消息，有个洋妞过来了
There's a foreign lady coming.
收到了没有？
Do you hear me?
知道，知道了
Yes.
快把大懒猪叫起来
Wake him up! He's the laziest.
起来
Get up!
快快，小子，冷静点，不要怕
kid, take it easy. Don't be afraid.
我们精神上支持你
We give you spiritual support!
嗨
Hello!
你穿了什么？
What are you wearing?
运动服装
Sports wear.
脱了它
No, take it off!
不可以，不然就不走了
Without this, l won't go.
等一等…
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
他不肯脱
Boss, he won't do it.
带他回来这里
Bring him in.
下来
Get in!
嗨！
Hello!
不要摸
Don't touch!
你摸、他摸、她摸，砰砰砰…我摸
You touch, he touches, she touches...
如果你有诚意的话，先把衣服脱了
lf you are sincere, take off yourjacket.
当然有诚意，不然会单刀赴会吗？
Of course l'm sincere, or else l wouldn't be here alone!
他已经到了，在那边
He's here. Over there.
金刚，开过去
king kong, go over there.
快点，快点！
Hurry up.
我想到进去的办法了
l'll find a way to get in!
怎样进去？
How?
爬冷气口
Through the air-conditioner duct!
受不了！这么土的方法也想得出来
This is not a new idea at all!
算了算了…
Forget it...
我可真服了你
l really admire you!
兵马俑这么大的东西你也脱得了手
How did you sell the Terracotta Army?
我跟我姐姐有个景泰蓝花瓶
My Sis and l even can't sell an antique vase
半年都脱不了手
in half a year.
半价卖给你们算了
How about half price to you?
嗨！好久不见了
Hi Buddy! Long time no see!
我警告你，不准她摸我
Tell her not to touch me anymore.
你告诉她，不准再摸我了
-Bitch! -That's enough!
乱吃我豆腐
Don't touch me!
我的剑怎么了？
What about my sword?
我的小姐怎么了？
What about my girl?
丫头，别害怕，上面风景不错呀
Ellen, don't be afraid.
慢慢欣赏吧
Everything's fine now!
救命呀！喂…
Help, help...
救我啊！
Help me!
什么？什么？
What? What?
我说，他们刚才差点把我打死！
l say, they nearly kill me just then!
别吵！
Shut up.
不用怕，大过年的吉利点
Don't be afraid! We're here.
他死我们还没死哩！
We're luckier than them.
我们还是讲生意
Let's get down to business, shall we?
你做生意真是很厉害啊
You're a real businessman!
剑怎么样了？
How's the sword?
打开盒子
Open the box.
这么快便掏枪了？
Using a pistol already?
这次死定了
Too bad!
有事慢慢讲，先生
Take it easy man,
开枪！只要你开枪就大家一起死
Take it easy!
救我呀，快点来救我呀！快点呀
Help... Please help me!
你不要吵好不好？
keep quiet!
你没看到现在情况多紧张吗？
Can't you see the situation is getting tense here?
到那边去
Go over there.
不要乱来
Be calm!-What are you want?
现在几点了？时间！
-What's the time now?Time，time…
十二点
Twelve!
时间刚刚好
Perfect!
快把那个女的放了
Go release the girl now!
不然我就炸死你们
Or else l'll blow you up!
放了那女孩
Let go of that girl.
放我呀…快点！
Let me go...
快把她放了！
Let her go quickly!
捉住他
Get him!
快追
Hurry up!
追
After him.
金刚！
king kong!
不关我的事，我来看热闹的
l'm not part of it, just passing by!
居然没有事
Thank God l'm alright.
不要动
Don't move!
糟了
Oh, God!
把剑交给我
Give me the sword!
去死啦！
Go to hell!
不要开枪！小心兵马俑
Don't shoot! Mind the Terracottas!
踢他、揍他、打他、扁他…
Beat him... Beat him...
金刚，快踢
king kong, kick him!
金刚
king kong!
痛死我了！下来
lt hurts! Come on down!
别出声
Be quiet!
快点！
Be quick!
快点扔下来！
Come on throw it down!
你没事吧？
Are you alright?
没事！
Fine!
不要死撑着，快拿兵器给他们
Don't pretend. Go get them the arms.
我来挡着他们
l'll take care of them first!
你干什么？
What are you doing?
快去呀！快拿兵器给他们
Go... Go get them the arms!
快起来吧，我是可怜你
Get up! l just pity you.
我还是讨厌你的
But l still hate you!
光头佬接住
Baldy, take it.
你真是有够笨
You're really stupid!
让我劈死她，走…
Split her to death! Go... Go...
来…帮我打电话给华叔！
Come... Call Uncle Wah.
我说什么？
What should l tell him?
你会说的，快
You know what you should tell him! Go quick!
抢回它，我的剑
Get my sword, get my sword!
看你跑到那里去
You got nowhere to hide.
抓到了你…
l've got you!
是我呀
lt's me!
你这是干什么？
What're you doing?
认不出是我，那就不会杀我了嘛！
They won't kill me if they can't find me.
两个宇宙飞弹，谁认不出来？白痴！
You can't hide with 2 big bombs, idiot!
来
Come on!
走
Go!
人都不见了，先去拿剑吧！来
Go get the sword.
有电！
lt's electrified!
你这个胆小鬼，那有！看着吧
What a coward, what electricity?
真的有电！
They've electrified the sword!
怎么样？
What should we do?
走！快走
Go!
下去
Go down!
快把家伙给我
Get me the arms, quick!
我到那边去
l'll go over there!
好的
Okay.
去你妈
Go to hell!
这群家伙刀枪不入！
The Terracotta Army seems bullet-proof!
抓住他们…
Go get him, go get him!
绑住他们！快点，快…
Block them first, quick, quick!
上去拿剑吧
Go get the sword!
拿剑
Go!
你去拿
You go!
有电呀
There's electricity!
你不要告诉他嘛
You shouldn't tell him!
小王八蛋，有电你不告诉我？
You bastard!
你智商零蛋啊！你想电死我吗？
Are you trying to kill me?
姐姐，不要！有电！
Sis... No!
后面后面…拿到了！
Back, backward.
死啦！
Oh! Shit!
金刚
king kong
是
Yes!
怎么会是个女的？对不起
A woman! Excuse me.
来…来！来…来呀！
Come... Come... Come up!
走！  来呀！
光头佬
Baldy!
来，让你玩玩，好过瘾
Come on, it's fun!
以后不许偷国宝！知不知道？
Never steal the nation's treasure again, Ok?
你说什么？
What did you say?
还装蒜？知不知道？
Don't pretend!
知道
Yes!
你要是敢再做就把你阉了
lf you dare to do so, l'll castrate you!
快点来！不知道那个是真 那个是假的？
Come on! Which one is real and which one is fake?
别管那么多了 真的也砍，假的也砍！
Cut them all!
搞定了
Alright!
了不起
Good!
里面的人听着
Attention, everyone inside.
我们已经把你们全部包围
You are surrounded.
把武器快点放下
Put down your arms and surrender.
华叔呀  …出来投降
Uncle Wah! Come out to surrender.
现在怎么样了？
What's the situation now?
我已经全部搞定了！没问题
Everything has been settled.
情形怎么样了？  搞定了
-What shall we do now? -Go get your extra bonus.
搞定了还叫我来干什么？
Why did you ask me to come then?
叫你来是要送份礼物给你
We have a gift for you.
你们两位一定是新最佳拍档了
You must be the ''New Aces''.
是呀，我姐姐
Yeah, my sister...
就是他们两个提议
They suggested we give you a gift
在你退休之前送你一份大礼
before you retire.
是吗？
Really?
是呀…
Yes...
那怎么好意思？
Good, thanks.
先谢了！我也有投票赞成
Thanks! l played my part too.
心领了
Thanks!
不过这份礼，最好送给中国蓝波
l think Chinese Rambo needs the gift
因为他比较需要！
more than me.
谢谢署长，谢谢…
Thank you!
谢谢…
Thank you...
送给你们
This is for you.
那四位最佳拍档呢？
Where are they?
不用等他们了，你要赶时间！
No need to wait, you are in a hurry.
好的，替我谢谢他们    好
-Tell them l really appreciate what they've done for me. -Ok.
再见
Goodbye!
发财有理，一发到底
Prosperity is reasonable, prosper to the end!
发财有理，一发到底…
没有钱，就没有明天
No money, no tomorrow!
向前看，不要看左右
Look ahead, don't look back.
新中国，请不要逼我走
Officers, please don't force me to go!
不想移民去外国
l don't want to emigrate!
我知道了，友谊万岁
l know! Friendship is forever.
友谊万岁！
Friendship forever!
伙计慢打锣，唏唏呵呵呵
Hey hey oh oh,
呢首叫乜S歌
What's the song's name?
我未惊过
l've never been frightened.
我细细个，已经好威猛事迹多多
l've done great deeds from an early age,
扮武松打虎打到只猎狗累低
Defeated even the hunting dogs.
班靓仔个个服我，叫我阿哥
The kids admired me and called me ''Big Brother''.
我未惊过
l've never been frightened.
有杀错没有放过
l'm merciless.
见靓女即上“My name is paul”
When l see a pretty girl, l'll say ''My name is Paul''.
撞正个妈打四百磅大肥婆
When l run into her 400 lbs mother.
渠黎手秤住我
who holds me suddenly and forces to Tango like fire,
要我跳似火探戈，我未惊过
l've never been frightened.
谁没有错，跌倒多少遍再站起过
Who's never done wrong? Just pick yourself up again.
路径坎坷不叹奈何
Don't complain about failures or hardships.
用我双手乾坤转过
Use my hand to change my fate.
无论挫折有几多，我未惊过
No matter how many setbacks, l've never been frightened.
唏唏呵呵！我未惊过
Hey hey oh oh, l'm never scared!